<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Setting the scene on Diversity &amp; Inclusion in Science (better title TBD)</title>
    <link>https://Pawsey-Internships.github.io/diversity_inclusion_workshop/introduction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Setting the scene on Diversity &amp; Inclusion in Science (better title TBD)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 10:42:40 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Pawsey-Internships.github.io/diversity_inclusion_workshop/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Approaching the workshop</title>
      <link>https://Pawsey-Internships.github.io/diversity_inclusion_workshop/introduction/participation_requests/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 17:06:34 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Pawsey-Internships.github.io/diversity_inclusion_workshop/introduction/participation_requests/</guid>
      <description>Approaching the workshop: some requests As we move through the workshop today, we ask that everyone:
Be ready to participate. Use welcoming and inclusive language. Be respectful of different viewpoints and experiences. Gracefully accept constructive criticism. If you feel like you need support at any time during the workshop, mesasge one of the mentors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Definitions</title>
      <link>https://Pawsey-Internships.github.io/diversity_inclusion_workshop/introduction/definitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 18:11:32 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Pawsey-Internships.github.io/diversity_inclusion_workshop/introduction/definitions/</guid>
      <description>What do we mean? Bias is a prejudice towards or against a specific group.
Diversity can refer to the mix of people in an organisation, or datapoints in your sample.
Inclusion is the outcome of behaviours promiting an environment where diverse people (or data points) can thrive. In an organisation, maximising inclusion also improves overall performance and wellbeing. Insert source?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work and Workplace</title>
      <link>https://Pawsey-Internships.github.io/diversity_inclusion_workshop/introduction/work-and-workplace/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 11:18:16 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Pawsey-Internships.github.io/diversity_inclusion_workshop/introduction/work-and-workplace/</guid>
      <description>Our work and workplace In the workplace, inclusion means:
Equitable access to the resources, training, support, and recognition needed to excel. Feeling welcome, respected and valued. Acknowledging differences and how they can contribute to positive outcomes. Diversity and inclusion is consistent with Australia’s identity as a multicultural and egalitarian society.
The day-to-day work of science, engineering and other ‘technical’ fields can feel removed from social issues, but our work is highly collaborative and driven by its potential for a positive impact on the world at large.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Overview</title>
      <link>https://Pawsey-Internships.github.io/diversity_inclusion_workshop/introduction/workshop-takeaways/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 11:15:35 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Pawsey-Internships.github.io/diversity_inclusion_workshop/introduction/workshop-takeaways/</guid>
      <description>Workshop Overview Include a summary here once we have a clear idea of workshop structure.
All human interactions and observations are unavoidably biased - including how we work in science. Biases can be helpful or unhelpful, but we cannot make that judgement without first identifying and understanding them. The more diversity you see around you the more your horizons expand in your work and your understanding Being open to tools and types of working allows us to identify these biases and begin to correct for unhelpful ones.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
